Guide to the North Carolina State University School of Design Historic Architecture Research Project Records, 1951-1976 UA 110.041
Special Collections Research Center
- UA 110.041 Series 1: Projects, 1951-1976; 32.75 linear feet 369 flat folders, 23 archival boxes, and 1 archival half box
  - Georgia, Camden County, Cumberland Island: Plantation Office Drawings [sheet #1 missing], 3 drawings (Folder 80.1)
  - Georgia, Camden County, Cumberland Island: Plantation Office Field notes (Box 4, Folder 80.2)
  - Georgia, Camden County, Cumberland Island: Plantation Office Photographs (Box 4, Folder 80.3)
  - Georgia, Camden County, Cumberland Island: Plantation Office Photographs (Box 4, Folder 80.4)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Williamsboro: St. John's Episcopal Church [same as project 147] Drawings, 16 drawings (Folder 81.1)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Williamsboro: St. John's Episcopal Church [same as project 147] Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 81.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Wake Forest: Calvin Jones House Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 82.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Wake Forest: Calvin Jones House Field notes (Box 4, Folder 82.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Moravian Church Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 83.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Moravian Church Field notes (Box 4, Folder 83.2)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County: Cedar Grove, Torrance House Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 84.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County: Cedar Grove, Torrance House Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 84.2)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Old Market House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 85.1)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Old Market House Mounted photographs (Folder 85.2)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Old Market House Mounted photographs (Box 4, Folder 85.3)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Old Market House Mounted photographs (Box 4, Folder 85.4)
  - North Carolina, Cumberland County, Fayetteville: Old Market House Field notes, reduced drawings (Box 4, Folder 85.5)
  - North Carolina, Davidson County, Lexington: Davidson County Courthouse Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 86.1)
  - North Carolina, Davidson County, Lexington: Davidson County Courthouse Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 86.2)
  - North Carolina, Edgecombe County, Tarboro: Cotton Press Drawings, 3 drawings (Folder 87.1)
  - North Carolina, Edgecombe County, Tarboro: Cotton Press Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 87.2)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Yanceyville: Caswell County Courthouse Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 88.1)
  - North Carolina, Caswell County, Yanceyville: Caswell County Courthouse Field notes (Box 4, Folder 88.2)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Skyland: Old Gasperson Cabin Drawings, 2 drawings (Folder 89.1)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Skyland: Old Gasperson Cabin Field notes (Box 4, Folder 89.2)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Parsonage Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 90.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Bethabara: Parsonage Field notes (Box 4, Folder 90.2)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County, Como: Hare Plantation Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 91.1)
  - North Carolina, Hertford County, Como: Hare Plantation Field notes (Box 4, Folder 91.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: St. James Episcopal Church Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 92.1)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: St. James Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 92.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Chief Justice Thomas Ruffin's Law Office at Burnside Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 93.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Chief Justice Thomas Ruffin's Law Office at Burnside Field notes, photographs (Box 4, Folder 93.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Orange County Courthouse Drawings, 20 drawings (Folder 94.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Orange County Courthouse Field notes (Box 5, Folder 94.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: Orange County Courthouse Photographs, reduced drawings (Box 5, Folder 94.3)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, High Point: Quaker Meeting House Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 95.1)
  - North Carolina, Guilford County, High Point: Quaker Meeting House Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 95.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Granite Quarry: Old Stone House [same as project 60] Drawings, 3 drawings (Folder 96.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Granite Quarry: Old Stone House [same as project 60] Field notes (Box 5, Folder 96.2)
  - North Carolina, Rutherford County: Cleghorn Plantation House Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 97.1)
  - North Carolina, Rutherford County: Cleghorn Plantation House Field notes, photograph (Box 5, Folder 97.2)
  - North Carolina, Stanly County: Home of Dr. Francis Joseph Kron Drawings, 3 drawings (Folder 98.1)
  - North Carolina, Stanly County: Home of Dr. Francis Joseph Kron Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 98.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Rectory [former Bank of the State of North Carolina] Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 99.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Christ Episcopal Church Rectory [former Bank of the State of North Carolina] Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 99.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Dortch House Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 100.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Dortch House Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 100.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Mordecai House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 101.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Mordecai House Field notes (Box 5, Folder 101.2)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: St. Stephen's Episcopal Church Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 102.1)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: St. Stephen's Episcopal Church Field notes (Box 5, Folder 102.2)
  - Virginia, Hot Springs: Christ Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 103.1)
  - Virginia, Hot Springs: Christ Church Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 103.2)
  - Virginia, Richmond: John Marshall House Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 104.1)
  - Virginia, Richmond: John Marshall House Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 104.2)
  - Virginia, Fort Monroe: Fort Monroe Main Gate Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 105.1)
  - Virginia, Fort Monroe: Fort Monroe Main Gate Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 105.2)
  - Florida, Monroe County, Key West: Ernest Hemingway House Field notes, photographs [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 5, Folder 106.1)
  - North Carolina, Anson County, Ansonville: The Oaks, General Smith's House Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 107.1)
  - North Carolina, Anson County, Ansonville: The Oaks, General Smith's House Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 107.2)
  - North Carolina, Wilson County, Wilson: P.D. Gold Publishing Co. Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 108.1)
  - North Carolina, Wilson County, Wilson: P.D. Gold Publishing Co. Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 5, Folder 108.2)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: Primitive Baptist Church (former First Methodist) Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 109.1)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: Primitive Baptist Church (former First Methodist) Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 5, Folder 109.2)
  - Connecticut, New Haven County, Guilford: Henry Whitfield House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 110.1)
  - Connecticut, New Haven County, Guilford: Henry Whitfield House Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 110.2)
  - Virginia, Fairfax County: Ossian Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 111.1)
  - Virginia, Fairfax County: Ossian Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 111.2)
  - South Carolina, Kershaw County, Camden: Old Courthouse Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 112.1)
  - South Carolina, Kershaw County, Camden: Old Courthouse Field notes, photographs (Box 5, Folder 112.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Asheboro: Old Female Academy Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 113.1)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County, Asheboro: Old Female Academy Field notes (Box 5, Folder 113.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Bellamy Mansion Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 114.1)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Bellamy Mansion Field notes (Box 6, Folder 114.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: Bellamy Mansion Photographs, negatives (Box 6, Folder 114.3)
  - New York, Erie County, Buffalo: 1833 Harbor Lighthouse Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 115.1)
  - New York, Erie County, Buffalo: 1833 Harbor Lighthouse Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 6, Folder 115.2)
  - Ohio, Lucas County, Maumee: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 116.1)
  - Ohio, Lucas County, Maumee: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs (Box 6, Folder 116.2)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Asheville: McDowell Residence [same as McDowell House, project no. 129] Field notes, photographs [drawings in project no. 129], 0 drawings (Box 6, Folder 117.1)
  - Mississippi, Hinds County, Clinton: Mississippi College Chapel Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 118.1)
  - Mississippi, Hinds County, Clinton: Mississippi College Chapel Field notes, photographs (Box 6, Folder 118.2)
  - North Carolina, Catawba County, Claremont vicinity: Bunker Hill Covered Bridge over Lyle Creek [same as project no. 241] Field notes [drawings missing] (Box 6, Folder 119.1)
  - North Carolina, Washington County (item reads Tyrrell County): Josiah Collins House, Lake Phelps [Somerset Place] Field notes, photographs [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 6, Folder 120.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Winston-Salem (Old Salem): Tinsmith Shop of Philip Reich Drawings [field notes missing], 6 drawings (Folder 121.1)
  - North Carolina, Nash County, Rocky Mount: Battle Home Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 122.1)
  - North Carolina, Nash County, Rocky Mount: Battle Home Field notes (Box 6, Folder 122.2)
  - North Carolina, Nash County, Rocky Mount: Battle Home Photographs, negatives (Box 6, Folder 122.3)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, McAdenville: McAden Mills No. 2 Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 123.1)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, McAdenville: McAden Mills No. 2 Field notes, photograph (Box 6, Folder 123.2)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Halifax: Old Gaol and Clerk of Court's Office Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 124.1)
  - North Carolina, Halifax County, Halifax: Old Gaol and Clerk of Court's Office Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 6, Folder 124.2)
  - Rhode Island, Providence County, Lincoln: Israel Arnold House Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 125.1)
  - Rhode Island, Providence County, Lincoln: Israel Arnold House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 6, Folder 125.2)
  - Georgia, Jefferson County, Louisville: Slave Market Drawings, 1 drawing (Folder 126.1)
  - South Carolina, Myrtle Beach: Kitchen, Brookgreen Gardens Drawings, 2 drawings (Folder 126.1)
  - Georgia, Jefferson County, Louisville: Slave Market Field notes (Box 6, Folder 126.2)
  - South Carolina, Myrtle Beach: Kitchen, Brookgreen Gardens Field notes (Box 6, Folder 126.2)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: St. Mary's Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 127.1)
  - North Carolina, Orange County, Hillsborough: St. Mary's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, proposals for alternative projects (Box 6, Folder 127.2)
  - New York, Suffolk County, Lloyd Harbor: Leffert's Grist Mill Field notes, photographs [drawings missing], 0 drawings (Box 6, Folder 128.1)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Asheville: McDowell House [same as McDowell Residence, project no. 117] Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 129.1)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County, Asheville: McDowell House [same as McDowell Residence, project no. 117] Field notes (Box 6, Folder 129.2)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County: Old Randolph Bridge no. 52 Drawings, 2 drawings (Folder 130.1)
  - North Carolina, Randolph County: Old Randolph Bridge no. 52 Field notes, photographs (Box 6, Folder 130.2)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County: Birthplace of Zebulon B. Vance Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 131.1)
  - North Carolina, Buncombe County: Birthplace of Zebulon B. Vance Field notes, photograph (Box 6, Folder 131.2)
  - Virginia, Gloucester County, Gloucester: Ware Church Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 132.1)
  - Virginia, Gloucester County, Gloucester: Ware Church Field notes, photographs (Box 6, Folder 132.2)
  - Tennessee, Sullivan County, Kingsport: Netherland Inn Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 133.1)
  - Tennessee, Sullivan County, Kingsport: Netherland Inn Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 7, Folder 133.2)
  - Virginia, Hampton: St. John's Church Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 134.1)
  - Virginia, Hampton: St. John's Church Field notes, photographs (Box 7, Folder 134.2)
  - North Carolina, Durham County: Fairntosh Farm Office Buildings Drawings [some missing] [field notes missing], 16 drawings (Folder 135.1)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County: Ramsaur Grinding Mill Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 136.1)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County: Ramsaur Grinding Mill Field notes (Box 7, Folder 136.2)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County: Ramsaur Grinding Mill Photographs (Box 7, Folder 136.3)
  - Louisiana, New Orleans: St. Louis Cemetery No. 2 Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 137.1)
  - Louisiana, New Orleans: St. Louis Cemetery No. 2 Field notes, photographs (Box 7, Folder 137.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Washington: Warehouses Drawings, 21 drawings (Folder 138.1)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Washington: Warehouses Oversized sketches (Folder 138.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Washington: Warehouses Field notes, photographs (Box 7, Folder 138.3)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Kernersville: Korner's Folly Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 139.1)
  - North Carolina, Forsyth County, Kernersville: Korner's Folly Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 7, Folder 139.2)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia County, Philadelphia: Town House in Society Hill Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 140.1)
  - Pennsylvania, Philadelphia County, Philadelphia: Town House in Society Hill Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 7, Folder 140.2)
  - New Jersey, Union County, Plainfield: Friends Meeting House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 141.1)
  - New Jersey, Union County, Plainfield: Friends Meeting House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 7, Folder 141.2)
  - North Carolina, Richmond County, Rockingham: Great Falls Mill Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 142.1)
  - North Carolina, Richmond County, Rockingham: Great Falls Mill Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 7, Folder 142.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Bath: Bonner House Drawings [field notes missing], 8 drawings (Folder 143.1)
  - North Carolina, Dare County, Duck vicinity: Caffey's Inlet Life-Saving Station Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 144.1)
  - North Carolina, Dare County, Duck vicinity: Caffey's Inlet Life-Saving Station Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 7, Folder 144.2)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 145.1)
  - North Carolina, Carteret County, Beaufort: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 7, Folder 145.2)
  - Tennessee, Sullivan County, Blountville: Old Deery Inn Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 146.1)
  - Tennessee, Sullivan County, Blountville: Old Deery Inn Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 7, Folder 146.2)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Williamsboro: St. John's Episcopal Church [same as project 81] Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 147.1)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Williamsboro: St. John's Episcopal Church [same as project 81] Oversized sketches (Folder 147.2)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Williamsboro: St. John's Episcopal Church [same as project 81] Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 7, Folder 147.3)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Charlotte: Alexander House [same as project 49] Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 148.1)
  - North Carolina, Mecklenburg County, Charlotte: Alexander House [same as project 49]Field notes, photographs (Box 7, Folder 148.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Swift Creek township: Barney Jones Farm Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 149.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Swift Creek township: Barney Jones Farm Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 8, Folder 149.2)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: St. John's Lodge Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 150.1)
  - North Carolina, New Hanover County, Wilmington: St. John's Lodge Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 8, Folder 150.2)
  - North Carolina, Union County, Monroe: Drury Morgan Mill Drawings, 4 drawings (Folder 151.1)
  - North Carolina, Union County, Monroe: Drury Morgan Mill Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 8, Folder 151.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Raleigh's First Post Office; Storefronts, 108 & 110 E. Hargett St., 126 E. Martin St.Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 152.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Raleigh's First Post Office; Storefronts, 108 & 110 E. Hargett St., 126 E. Martin St.Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 8, Folder 152.2)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: Well House Drawings, 5 drawings (Folder 153.1)
  - North Carolina, Wayne County, Goldsboro: Well House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 8, Folder 153.2)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Lincolnton: Ingleside Drawings, 15 drawings (Folder 154.1)
  - North Carolina, Lincoln County, Lincolnton: Ingleside Field notes (Box 8, Folder 154.2)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Organ Zion Lutheran Church Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 155.1)
  - North Carolina, Rowan County, Salisbury: Organ Zion Lutheran Church Field notes, photographs, color slides, proposal for alternative project (Lowerstone Church) (Box 8, Folder 155.2)
  - Germany, Berlin: Sankt Annen Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 156.1)
  - Germany, Berlin: Sankt Annen Church Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 156.2)
  - Mexico: Zapotec Ball Court Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 157.1)
  - Mexico: Zapotec Ball Court Field notes, photograph (Box 8, Folder 157.2)
  - North Carolina, Johnston County, Bentonville: Harper House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 158.1)
  - North Carolina, Johnston County, Bentonville: Harper House Field notes, photograph, negative (Box 8, Folder 158.2)
  - North Carolina, Burke County, Morganton: Pleasant Valley, Perkins Farm House Drawings, 11 drawings (Folder 159.1)
  - North Carolina, Burke County, Morganton: Pleasant Valley, Perkins Farm House Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 159.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: North Carolina State Capitol Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 160.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: North Carolina State Capitol Field notes (Box 8, Folder 160.2)
  - North Carolina, Union County, Mineral Springs: Pleasant Grove Methodist Camp Ground Arbor Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 161.1)
  - North Carolina, Union County, Mineral Springs: Pleasant Grove Methodist Camp Ground Arbor Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 161.2)
  - North Carolina, Scotland County, Wagram: Richmond Temperance & Literary Society Hall Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 162.1)
  - North Carolina, Scotland County, Wagram: Richmond Temperance & Literary Society Hall Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 162.2)
  - Virginia, Smyth County, Thomas Bridge Community near Marion Township: Abijah Thomas House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 163.1)
  - Virginia, Smyth County, Thomas Bridge Community near Marion Township: Abijah Thomas House Oversized sketches (Folder 163.2)
  - Virginia, Smyth County, Thomas Bridge Community near Marion Township: Abijah Thomas House Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 8, Folder 163.3)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Henderson: Ashland Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 164.1)
  - North Carolina, Vance County, Henderson: Ashland Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 164.2)
  - Alabama, Clebourne County, Edwardsville: Old Clebourne County Courthouse Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 165.1)
  - Alabama, Clebourne County, Edwardsville: Old Clebourne County Courthouse Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 165.2)
  - North Carolina, Davie County, Mocksville: Cooleemee Plantation Drawings, 14 drawings (Folder 166.1)
  - North Carolina, Davie County, Mocksville: Cooleemee Plantation Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 166.2)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Washington: Hollyday House (formerly Brown House)Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 167.1)
  - North Carolina, Beaufort County, Washington: Hollyday House (formerly Brown House)Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 8, Folder 167.2)
  - New Jersey, Bergen County, North Hackensack: Old 1678 Demarest House Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 168.1)
  - New Jersey, Bergen County, North Hackensack: Old 1678 Demarest House Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 168.2)
  - Virginia, Northampton County, Jamesville: Mattissippi or Sturgis Place Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 169.1)
  - Virginia, Northampton County, Jamesville: Mattissippi or Sturgis Place Field notes, photographs (Box 8, Folder 169.2)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, Dallas: Old Gaston County Courthouse Drawings, 6 drawings (Folder 170.1)
  - North Carolina, Gaston County, Dallas: Old Gaston County Courthouse Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 170.2)
  - New York, Westchester County, Larchmont: Manor House Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 171.1)
  - New York, Westchester County, Larchmont: Manor House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 171.2)
  - Massachusetts, Barnstable County, Eastham: Swift House Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 172.1)
  - Massachusetts, Barnstable County, Eastham: Swift House Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 172.2)
  - North Carolina, Henderson County, Fletcher: Westfeldt Estate, Rugby Grange Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 173.1)
  - North Carolina, Henderson County, Fletcher: Westfeldt Estate, Rugby Grange Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 173.2)
  - North Carolina, Washington County, Creswell: St. David's Episcopal Church Drawings, 10 drawings (Folder 174.1)
  - North Carolina, Washington County, Creswell: St. David's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 174.2)
  - North Carolina, Alexander County, Taylorsville: Alexander County Courthouse Drawings, 7 drawings (Folder 175.1)
  - North Carolina, Alexander County, Taylorsville: Alexander County Courthouse Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 175.2)
  - North Carolina, Alamance County, Burlington: St. Athanasius Episcopal Church Drawings, 13 drawings (Folder 176.1)
  - North Carolina, Alamance County, Burlington: St. Athanasius Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 176.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Wake Forest vicinity: Old Dempsey Powell House Drawings, 9 drawings (Folder 177.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Wake Forest vicinity: Old Dempsey Powell House Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 177.2)
  - Tennessee, Carter County, Elizabethton: Elizabethton Covered Bridge Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 178.1)
  - Tennessee, Carter County, Elizabethton: Elizabethton Covered Bridge Field notes, photographs (Box 9, Folder 178.2)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Tucker House Carriage House/Stable Drawings, 12 drawings (Folder 179.1)
  - North Carolina, Wake County, Raleigh: Tucker House Carriage House/Stable Field notes, photographs, negative (Box 9, Folder 179.2)
  - North Carolina, Wilkes County, Wilkesboro: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Drawings, 8 drawings (Folder 180.1)
  - North Carolina, Wilkes County, Wilkesboro: St. Paul's Episcopal Church Field notes, photographs, negatives (Box 9, Folder 180.2)